Commencement Programs; Collection ua935
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
Commencement Programs Collection
1857-2019
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
ua935
2 cubic ft. 3 Digital Files
This collection is made up of programs for commencement ceremonies at the University at Albany.
Administrative History
Commencement programs have been issued by the University at Albany and the previous institutions it existed as for many years. Early version from the State Normal School were fairly simple, listing attending staff, some of the musical selections, and the short list of graduates that might take up a single page. They have expanded greatly since then, not only because of the growth in students and faculty at the institution, as well as the expanded nature of the event.
Scope and Contents
This collection consists of the programs for commencement ceremonies from the years 1857 to 2019. The years 1857-1908 are not complete, with various copies missing. From 1910 on every version is in the collection, with the inclusion of the winter commencement programs beginning in 2001 until 2016. Within these programs can be found complete lists of graduates of each various program, faculty attendees, and the speakers who delivered speeches during the ceremony.
Arrangement of the Collection
Collection is arranged chronologically.
Acquisition Information
All items in this manuscript group were donated to the University Libraries, M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives.
Related Materials
Related collections in the M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives can be found in the subject guide for Criminal Justice and Prisons.
Access
Access to this record group is unrestricted.
Commencement ceremonies; Baccalaureate addresses; UAlbany Reference Collections; Digital Files
- Commencement Program, 1857 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Semi-Annual Exercise of the Literary Societies, 1860 January 27 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Commencement Program, 1860 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Commencement Program, 1861 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Semi-Annual Exercise of the Literary Societies, 1863 January 23 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Commencement Program, 1863 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Commencement Program, 1865 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Commencement Program, 1872 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Commencement Program, 1873 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Commencement Program, 1875 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Philomathean Society Closing Excercises, 1876 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Commencement Program for the 65th Term, 1877 January 30 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Commencement Program for the 66th Term, 1877 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Commencement Program, 1882 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Commencement Program, 1885 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Commencement Program, 1886 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Commencement Program, 1887 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Closing Exercises of the 91st Term, 1890 January 24 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Closing Exercises of the 1st Term, 1890 June 26 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Commencement Program, 1891 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Commencement Program, 1892 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Commencement Program, 1893 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Commencement Program, 1894 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Commencement Program, 1895 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Commencement Program, 1896 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Commencement Program, 1897 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Commencement Program, 1898 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Commencement Program, 1899 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Commencement Program, 1901 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Commencement Program, 1905 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Commencement Program, 1906 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Commencement Program, 1907 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Commencement Program, 1908 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Commencement Program, 1910 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Commencement Program, 1911 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Commencement Program, 1912 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Commencement Program, 1913 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Commencement Program, 1914 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Commencement Program, 1915 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Commencement Program, 1916 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Commencement Program, 1917 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Commencement Program, 1919 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Commencement Program, 1920 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Commencement Program, 1921 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Commencement Program, 1922 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Commencement Program, 1923 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Commencement Program, 1924 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Commencement Program, 1925 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Commencement Program, 1926 (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Commencement Program, 1927 (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Commencement Program, 1928 (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Commencement Program, 1929 (Box 1, Folder 52)
- Commencement Program, 1930 (Box 1, Folder 53)
- Commencement Program, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 54)
- Commencement Program, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 55)
- Commencement Program, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 56)
- Commencement Program, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 57)
- Commencement Program, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 58)
- Commencement Program, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 59)
- Commencement Program, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 60)
- Commencement Program, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 61)
- Commencement Program, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 62)
- Commencement Program, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 63)
- Commencement Program, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 64)
- Commencement Program, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 65)
- Commencement Program, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 66)
- Centennial of the New York State College for Teachers, 1944 May 6 (Box 1, Folder 67)
- Commencement Program, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 68)
- Commencement Program, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 69)
- Commencement Program, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 70)
- Commencement Program, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 71)
- Commencement Program, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 72)
- Commencement Program, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 73)
- Commencement Program, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 74)
- Commencement Program, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 75)
- Commencement Program, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 76)
- Commencement Program, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 77)
- Commencement Program, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 78)
- Commencement Program, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 79)
- Commencement Program, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 80)
- Commencement Program, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 81)
- Commencement Program, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 82)
- Commencement Program, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 83)
- Commencement Program, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 84)
- Commencement Program, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 85)
- Commencement Program, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 86)
- Commencement Program, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 87)
- Commencement Program, 1964 (Box 2A, Folder 1)
- Commencement Program, 1965 (Box 2A, Folder 2)
- Commencement Program, 1966 (Box 2A, Folder 3)
- Commencement Program, 1967 (Box 2A, Folder 4)
- Commencement Program, 1968 (Box 2A, Folder 5)
- Commencement Program, 1969 (Box 2A, Folder 6)
- Commencement Program, 1970 (Box 2A, Folder 7)
- Commencement Program, 1971 (Box 2A, Folder 8)
- Commencement Program, 1972 (Box 2A, Folder 9)
- Commencement Program, 1973 (Box 2A, Folder 10)
- Commencement Program, 1974 (Box 2A, Folder 11)
- Commencement Program, 1975 (Box 2A, Folder 12)
- Commencement Program, 1976 (Box 2A, Folder 13)
- Commencement Program, 1977 (Box 2A, Folder 14)
- Commencement Program, 1978 (Box 2A, Folder 15)
- Commencement Program, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Commencement Program, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Commencement Program, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Commencement Program, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Commencement Program, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Commencement Program, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Commencement Address by Arthur Schlesinger Jr., 1984 May 20
  - Commencement Memorandum, 1984 April 30
  - Commencement Program, 1984 May 20
- Commencement Program, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Commencement Invitation, 1985
  - Commencement Brochure, 1985
  - Commencement Memorandum, 1985 April 24
- Commencement Program, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Commencement Weekend Schedule, 1986
  - Commencement Invitation, 1986
- Commencement Program, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Commencement weekend schedule, 1987
- Commencement Program, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Commencement Programs, 1988
  - Commencement Schedule, 1988 May 15
  - Commencement Press Release, 1987 November 18
- Commencement Program, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Commencement Program, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Commencement Program, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Commencement Program, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Commencement Program, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Commencement Program, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Commencement Program, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Commencement Program, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Commencement Program, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Commencement Program, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Commencement Program, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Commencement Program, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Commencement Mailer, 2000
  - Commencement Brochure, 2000
- Commencement Program, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- December Commencement Program, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Commencement Program, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- December Commencement Program, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Commencement Program, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- December Commencement Program, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Additional Fall Honors, 2003
- Commencement Program, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Commencement Schedule, 2004
- Commencement Program, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- December Commencement Program, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Commencement Program, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- December Commencement Program, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Commencement Program, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- December Commencement Program, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Commencement Program, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Commencement Platform Party Script, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- December Commencement Program, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Commencement Program, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 35)
- December Commencement Program, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 36)
- Commencement Program, 2010 (Box 4, Folder 37)
- December Commencement Program, 2010 (Box 4, Folder 38)
- Commencement Program, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- December Commencement Program, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Commencement Program, 2012 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- December Commencement Program, 2012 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Commencement Program, 2013 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- December Commencement Program, 2013 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Commencement Program, 2014 May (Box 4, Folder 7)
- December Commencement Program, 2014 December (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Commencement Program, 2015 May (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Commencement Program, 2015 December (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Commencement Program, 2016 May (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Commencement Program, 2016 December (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Commencement Program, 2017 May (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Commencement Program - Graduate Ceremony, 2018 May 18-20 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Commencement Program - Undergraduate Ceremony, 2018 May 20 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Commencement Program, 2019 May (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Commencement Program - Graduate Ceremony, 2020 May
- Commencement Program - Undergraduate Ceremony, 2020 May
- Commencement Program, 2021 May
- Commencement Program, 2022 May